moneysavingqueen.com 2014-11-21

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) describes the information collection, use and disclosure practices of the Internet Web Site of Money Saving Queen, located on the World Wide Web at [http://www.moneysavingqueen.com](http://www.moneysavingqueen.com/) (the “Web Site”). This Policy does not describe the privacy practices of any other company or entity, and does not govern the collection, use or disclosure of personal information by means of mail, telephone or any other communications channel other than the Money Saving Queen Web Site.

Our privacy practices are set out in this Policy and in no other document, and your use of our Web Site constitutes your acceptance of the terms of this Policy. This Policy may be changed from time to time, and you should visit our Web Site for notice of those changes. Your continued use of our Web Site after such changes are made constitutes your acceptance of those changes.

####  **_What Personal Information Do We Collect and Why Do We Collect It?_**

We collect four categories of information from visitors and other users of our Web Site: personal information, aggregate information, clickstream data, and cookie transmissions. The kinds of information contained within these categories, and the purposes for which we collect that information, are described below.

_Personal information_ we collect may include your name, postal address, e-mail address, date of birth, telephone number, payment card data and other information. We collect such items of personal information: (1) to respond to your requests for information; (2) to enroll you in contests in which you have asked to participate; (3) in your responses to surveys; (4) to process your requests for newsletters or participation in an RSS feeds; (5) to register you with the Web Site; or (6) to process your orders for products and services. Also, personal information collected on the Web Site may sometimes be combined with personal information obtained from third parties.

_Aggregate information_ is data derived from personal information submitted to our Web Site but not identifiable to individual persons. We may, for example, create a profile of our visitors according to zip codes and other factors that will help us to target our future marketing efforts. That aggregate information also might be made available to advertisers and potential advertisers, as we explain below.

_Clickstream data_ is nonpersonal information transmitted to us automatically from your computer when you interact with our Web Site. Clickstream data may include your computer’s IP address, the type of Web browser and operating system you are using, the pages and information you accessed on our Web Site, the time spent on our Web Site, and the domain name of a web site from which you linked to our Web Site. Information of this kind permits your computer to establish a working connection with our Web Site and navigate the Web Site more effectively. Clickstream data will not be used to identify you personally and will not be associated or correlated with any Web Site visitor or customer in a personally identifiable manner.

_Cookies_ are short strings of digitized text that the Web Site transmits to your computer, and that will send certain information to our Web Site when you are connected with our service. Cookies are used to “remember” user names and passwords, so that you are not required to re-enter that information each time you visit our Web Site. We also use cookies to understand which parts of our Web Site are most popular, where our visitors are going on our service and how much time they spend there. Cookies are read only by the server that placed them, and are unable to execute any code or virus.

If you do not want to have cookies stored on your computer, you may instruct your browser to block them, erase them or warn you before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions. However, blocking or erasing cookies may prevent you from using some of the functionalities of our Web Site.

Some uses of cookies in connection with our Web Site may be under the control of unaffiliated entities that we retain to process inquiries or orders, as further described below. We cannot be responsible for the uses of cookies by unaffiliated third parties.

####  **_When and to Whom Do We Disclose Information Collected on Our Web Site?_**

We do not sell your personal information to others. In some cases, we may refer your inquiries and product orders to independent companies that assist with the processing and fulfillment of those orders and inquiries. Also, if you agree to receive promotional materials, we may release personal information you provided when you registered with the Web Site to third party providers of goods or services that we believe might be of interest to you. We also may use your registration information to “pre-populate” forms provided at our Web Site. However, that information is not transmitted beyond the Web Site until the form is submitted. We also reserve the right to release personal information in our access logs concerning visitors who violate our Terms of Service or engage in illegal or harmful activity.

We require third parties to which we disclose information to use that information only for the intended purpose, and we prohibit third parties from selling or otherwise disclosing your personal information to third parties. We cannot, however, be responsible for any failure of those third parties to honor their privacy commitments to us. Similarly, we are not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of unaffiliated entity web sites that are linked to our Web Site.

We may compile aggregate information, as defined above, into reports that we provide to advertisers and potential advertisers. Those reports contain no information that permits their recipients to identify or contact individual persons.

We will disclose personal information concerning visitors and customers when required by legal process, or as necessary to protect the rights and safety of ourselves, our customers or the public.

We may transfer personal information to a purchaser or successor entity in connection with the sale of Moneysavingqueen.com, its owner, a subsidiary or line of business associated with Moneysavingqueen.com, or substantially all of the assets of Moneysavingqueen.com, its owner or any of its subsidiaries, affiliates or lines of business.

####  **_How Do We Protect Information Submitted to Our Web Site?_**

You should be aware that the Internet, like other media of communication, is subject to unauthorized intrusion and compromise. No web site or computer network can guarantee that it will not be penetrated by hackers or suffer a security breach through technical or human failure. We take technical and administrative measures to protect your information. We cannot be responsible, however, for loss, corruption or unauthorized disclosure of personal information submitted to us.

####  **_Note to Parents_**

Our Web Site is not directed to children and does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. When we acquire actual knowledge that a visitor to our Web Site is under the age of 13, we will take appropriate measures to avoid collection of personal information from that visitor or to collect and use such information only in compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act and other applicable law.

####  **_How Can You Ask Questions About Our Privacy Policy and Access Your Personal Information?_**

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, wish to access your personal information, or request that we not use your personal information for a particular purpose, please follow the instructions posted at [http://moneysavingqueen.com/Contact/](mailto:info@MoneySavingQueen.com).

This Privacy Policy was last modified on September 7, 2011.

###  Disclosure Policy:

This policy is valid from 16 December 2011

For questions about this blog, please contact moneysavingqueen2014@gmail.com.

This blog accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions or other forms of compensation.

 This blog abides by word of mouth marketing standards. We believe in honesty of relationship, opinion and identity. The compensation received may influence the advertising content, topics or posts made in this blog. That content, advertising space or post will be clearly identified as paid or sponsored content.

 The owner of this blog is compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. Even though the owner(s) of this blog receives compensation for our posts or advertisements, we always give our honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences on those topics or products. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely the bloggers' own. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question.

Money Saving Queen, LLC
